Guide to the International Brotherhood of Teamsters Leo Deaner collection 1902-2006 IBT0022
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Teamsters History, 1902-2006; Series 2; 4.5 Linear Feet
  - Local 776 Administrative Records, 1940-1998; Series 2 Subseries 4
    - Local 776-Charges and Correspondence, January-May, 1947; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Box 48, Folder 6)
    - Internal IBt Correspondence, May-December, 1948; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Box 48, Folder 7)
    - Local 776 Tax Records [1], 1949; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Box 48, Folder 8)
    - Local 776 Tax Records [2], 1950; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Box 48, Folder 9)
    - Local 776 Tax Records [3], 1951; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Box 48, Folder 10)
    - Local 776 Tax Records [4], 1952; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Box 48, Folder 11)
    - Local 776 Tax Records [5], 1953; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Box 48, Folder 12)
    - Local 776 Tax Records [6], 1975; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Box 48, Folder 13)
    - Local 776 Tax Records [7], 1978; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Box 48, Folder 14)
    - Local 776 Tax Records [8], 1979; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Box 48, Folder 15)
    - Local 776 Tax Records [9], 1982; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Box 48, Folder 16)
    - Local 776 Tax Records [10], 1983; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Box 48, Folder 17)
    - Local 776 Tax Records [11], 1984; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Box 48, Folder 18)
    - Local 776 Tax Records [12], 1985; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Box 48, Folder 19)
    - Local 776 Tax Records [13], 1986; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Box 48, Folder 20)
    - Local 776 Tax Records [14], 1987; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Box 48, Folder 21)
    - Local 776 Tax Records [15], 1989; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Box 48, Folder 22)
    - Local 776 Financial Reports and Tax Records [16], 1988-1991; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Box 48, Folder 23)
    - Union Dues-Correspondence and Booklet, April 1942-September 1952; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Box 52, Folder 1)
    - Local 776 New Members List [1], January-December 1949; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Box 52, Folder 2)
    - Local 776 New Members List [2], October-November 1948; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Box 52, Folder 3)
    - Local 776 New Members List [3], January-December 1950; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 52, Folder 4)
    - Local 776 New Members List [4], 1951; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Box 52, Folder 5)
    - Local 776 New Members List [5], January-December 1952; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Box 52, Folder 6)
    - Local 776 New Members List [6], January-April 1953; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Box 52, Folder 7)
    - Philadelphia Health and Welfare Fund, January 1953-March 1955; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Box 52, Folder 8)
    - Harrisburg Rent Control Statements, 1953; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Box 52, Folder 9)
    - Election Hearings and Charges, December 1957-January 1958; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Box 52, Folder 10)
    - "The Patriot"-Road Drivers News articles, January 5-12, 1959; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Box 52, Folder 11)
    - "The New Era"-Hoffa articles, April 16, 1959; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Box 52, Folder 12)
    - Follmer-Arthur Rosen Booklet, 1960; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Box 52, Folder 13)
    - 6 Highway Planning Commision Articles, 1960; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Box 52, Folder 14)
    - Scanton-Harrisburg Softball Team Photos, September 25, 1960; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Box 52, Folder 15)
    - Local 429-Health and Welfare Fund Report, August 1962-July 1963; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Box 52, Folder 16)
    - DRIVE [1], 1964-1982; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Box 52, Folder 17)
    - DRIVE [2], 1984-1986; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Box 52, Folder 18)
    - DRIVE [3], 1988; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Box 52, Folder 19)
    - DRIVE [4], 1989; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Box 52, Folder 20)
    - DRIVE [5], 1990; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Box 52, Folder 21)
    - DRIVE [6], 1991-1992; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Box 52, Folder 22)
    - Paul Carnathan Charges, April 13, 1970; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Box 52, Folder 23)
    - Grievances and Complaint Logs, 19701-1981; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Box 52, Folder 24)
    - Local 776 Correspondence, 1971-1990; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Box 52, Folder 25)
    - Teamsters-Credit Union [1], 1974-1987; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Box 52, Folder 26)
    - Teamsters-Credit Union [2], 1990-1991; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Box 52, Folder 27)
    - Teamster Magazine clippings, 1979-1984; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Box 52, Folder 28)
    - Initiation Increase Memo, September 17, 1985; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Box 53, Folder 1)
    - Local 776-Amendment Surveys, 1985-1986; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Box 53, Folder 2)
    - Business Agent Meetings [1], 1985; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Box 53, Folder 3)
    - Business Agent Meetings [2], 1988-1990; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Box 53, Folder 4)
    - Business Agent Meetings [3], 1991; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Box 53, Folder 5)
    - Business Agent Meetings [4], 1992-1993; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Box 53, Folder 6)
    - Weekly Agenda Logs [1], 1985-1987; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Box 53, Folder 7)
    - Weekly Agenda Logs [2], 1988-1990; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Box 53, Folder 8)
    - Weekly Agenda Logs [3], 1991-1993; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Box 53, Folder 9)
    - Local 776 Retirees Club, June 1986-November 1998; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Box 53, Folder 10)
    - Stewards-Local 776 [1], 1986-1987; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Box 53, Folder 11)
    - Stewards-Local 776 [2], 1988; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Box 53, Folder 12)
    - Stewards-Local 776 [3], 1989; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Box 53, Folder 13)
    - Stewards-Local 776 [4], 1990; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Box 53, Folder 14)
    - Stewards-Local 776 [5], 1991; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Box 53, Folder 15)
    - Stewards-Local 776 [6], 1992; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Box 53, Folder 16)
    - Stewards-Local 776 [7], 1993; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Box 53, Folder 17)
    - Local 776-Health and Welfare Fund Survey, 1988; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Box 53, Folder 18)
    - "Truckers Guide to Pennsylvania" pamphlet, undated; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Box 54, Folder 1)
    - Employers List-Local 776, undated; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Box 54, Folder 2)
    - Commercial Drivers License Seminar, 1989; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Box 54, Folder 3)
    - Hurricane Hugo-local 776 efforts, 1989; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Box 54, Folder 4)
    - Jurisdiction issue-Local 776, August, 1989; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Box 54, Folder 5)
    - Pennsylvania Conference of Teamsters, 1989; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Box 54, Folder 6)
    - Pennsylvania Labor Communications Association, 1989-1990; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Box 54, Folder 7)
    - Pittston Strike Photos, 1989; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Box 54, Folder 8)
    - Obituaries, 1989; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Box 54, Folder 9)
    - New Membership correspondence [1], 1989-1991; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Box 54, Folder 10)
    - New Membership correspondence [2], 1992-1993; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Box 54, Folder 11)
    - Stewards List, 1989-1990; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Box 54, Folder 12)
    - Deaner-Correspondence and Expense Records, 1990-1993; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Box 54, Folder 13)
    - Labor Day-Carlisle, Pa. Strike, October, 1990; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Box 54, Folder 14)
    - IBT Magazine Article-Correspondence, February 1991-March 1992; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Box 54, Folder 15)
    - Accident Insurance-Local 776, June, 1991; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Box 54, Folder 16)
    - Local 776 Constitutional Supplements, 1991; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Box 54, Folder 17)
    - Local 776 Scholarships, 1991; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Box 54, Folder 18)
    - Desert Storm, 1991; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Box 54, Folder 19)
    - Eastern Conference of Teamsters-Leo Deaner, 1992; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Box 54, Folder 20)
    - Ethical Practices Committee Charges against Daniel Virtue, 1992-1993; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Box 54, Folder 21)
    - Movie Extra-Local 776 Crew, May 12, 1992; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Box 54, Folder 22)
    - Tom Griffith Correspondence, 1992-1993; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Box 54, Folder 23)
    - Movie Film: "Thousand Islands", undated; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Box 55)
    - Videocassette-"Awards, Entertainment", October 31, 1987; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Box 55)
    - Videocassette-"Social, Tile room, Mr. Griffith", October 31, 1987; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Box 55)
  - National Labor Relations Board Suit: Leo Deaner and Central Storage and Transfer Co., Series 2 Subseries 5
    - Charge [1], February-March 1981; Series 2 Subseries 5 (Box 49, Folder 1)
    - Charge [2], February 1981-September 1982; Series 2 Subseries 5 (Box 49, Folder 2)
    - Harmatz Decision, February 1982; Series 2 Subseries 5 (Box 49, Folder 3)
    - Central's Civil Suit, October 1981-1983; Series 2 Subseries 5 (Box 49, Folder 4)
    - Eastern Express Blacklisting, 1979-1982; Series 2 Subseries 5 (Box 49, Folder 5)
    - NLRB in support of Harmatz, 1982; Series 2 Subseries 5 (Box 49, Folder 6)
    - NLRB Appeals Decision, 1982; Series 2 Subseries 5 (Box 49, Folder 7)
    - Charges Against Moudy at Local Union [1], 1983; Series 2 Subseries 5 (Box 49, Folder 8)
    - Charges Against Moudy at Local Union [2], 1981-1982; Series 2 Subseries 5 (Box 49, Folder 9)
    - Charges Against Moudy at Joint Council, 1982-1983; Series 2 Subseries 5 (Box 49, Folder 10)
    - Charles Leo Deaner Presentation/ Joint Council 53, 1982; Series 2 Subseries 5 (Box 49, Folder 11)
    - Letters to ECT & IBT, 1981; Series 2 Subseries 5 (Box 49, Folder 12)
    - Grievances, 1981-1982; Series 2 Subseries 5 (Box 49, Folder 13)
    - Boal in Support of Harmatz, 1982; Series 2 Subseries 5 (Box 49, Folder 14)
    - NLRB Ordered Posting, 1982; Series 2 Subseries 5 (Box 49, Folder 15)
    - Attorney Boal's Brief, 1981; Series 2 Subseries 5 (Box 49, Folder 16)
    - NLRB Official Transcript [1], November 2, 1981; Series 2 Subseries 5 (Box 50, Folder 1)
    - NLRB Official Transcript [2], November 2, 1981; Series 2 Subseries 5 (Box 50, Folder 2)
    - Clarification, 1981-1982; Series 2 Subseries 5 (Box 50, Folder 3)
    - Local 776 Agenda, 1982; Series 2 Subseries 5 (Box 50, Folder 4)
    - Central Storage Co. Training Program, 1980; Series 2 Subseries 5 (Box 50, Folder 5)
    - Central Storage Co. Contract, 1982-1983; Series 2 Subseries 5 (Box 50, Folder 6)
    - Discharge and NLRB Correspondence [1], 1981-1982; Series 2 Subseries 5 (Box 50, Folder 7)
    - Discharge and NLRB Correspondence [2], 1982-1983; Series 2 Subseries 5 (Box 50, Folder 8)
    - Monetary Settlement, 1982-1983; Series 2 Subseries 5 (Box 50, Folder 9)
    - Convoy Dispatch [1], April, 1980; Series 2 Subseries 5 (Box 51, Folder 1)
    - Convoy Dispatch [2], April, 1980; Series 2 Subseries 5 (Box 51, Folder 2)
    - Central Storage Co. Civil Case, 1980-1983; Series 2 Subseries 5 (Box 51, Folder 3)
    - Witness Statements, December 1980-January 1981; Series 2 Subseries 5 (Box 51, Folder 4)
    - NLRB Complaints, January-February, 1981; Series 2 Subseries 5 (Box 51, Folder 5)
    - NLRB Brief of Respondent [1], December, 1981; Series 2 Subseries 5 (Box 51, Folder 6)
    - NLRB Brief of Respondent [2], December, 1981; Series 2 Subseries 5 (Box 51, Folder 7)
    - Charles Leo Deaner Affidavit, January, 1981; Series 2 Subseries 5 (Box 51, Folder 8)
    - Central Storage Co. Brief on exceptions against Harmatz [1], 1982; Series 2 Subseries 5 (Box 51, Folder 9)
    - Central Storage Co. Brief on exceptions against Harmatz [2], 1982; Series 2 Subseries 5 (Box 51, Folder 10)
    - Flickinger Deposition in Civil Case, October, 1982; Series 2 Subseries 5 (Box 51, Folder 11)
    - Thomas Griffith Statement-Flickinger Subpoena, October 21, 1981; Series 2 Subseries 5 (Box 51, Folder 12)
    - Central Storage Co.-Newsclippings and Correspondence, September 1990-September 1991; Series 2 Subseries 5 (Box 51, Folder 13)
  - Newsletter-Local 776, 1982-1983; Series 2 (Box 44, Folder 1)
  - Teamsters Talk-TFT Newsletters, February-November 1979; Series 2 (Box 44, Folder 2)
  - Teamsters Talk-TFT Newsletters, December 1979-May 1980; Series 2 (Box 44, Folder 3)
  - Teamsters Talk-TFT Newsletters, September 1980-March 1981; Series 2 (Box 44, Folder 4)
  - Teamsters Talk-TFT Newsletters, April-September 1981; Series 2 (Box 44, Folder 5)
  - The Monthly Bulletin, September 1983-April 1984; Series 2 (Box 44, Folder 6)
  - The Monthly Bulletin-776 election, prior to vote, May-December 1984; Series 2 (Box 44, Folder 7)
  - The 776 Bulletin, 1985; Series 2 (Box 44, Folder 8)
  - The 776 Bulletin, 1986; Series 2 (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - The 776 Bulletin, 1987; Series 2 (Box 44, Folder 10)
  - The 776 Bulletin, 1988; Series 2 (Box 44, Folder 11)
  - The 776 Bulletin, 1989; Series 2 (Box 44, Folder 12)
  - The 776 Bulletin, 1990; Series 2 (Box 44, Folder 13)
  - The 776 Bulletin, 1991; Series 2 (Box 44, Folder 14)
  - The 776 Bulletin, 1992; Series 2 (Box 44, Folder 15)
  - The 776 Bulletin, 1993; Series 2 (Box 44, Folder 16)
  - Central Pennsylvania Teamster-Local 776 Publication, August 1973-June 1975; Series 2 (Box 44, Folder 17)
  - ABF-Drug Testing, 1984; Series 2 (Box 59, Folder 1)
  - ABF Freight Systems-Terminal Plan, 1987-1993; Series 2 (Box 59, Folder 2)
  - ABF-ESOP, 1987-1988; Series 2 (Box 59, Folder 3)
  - ABF-Kelso, May-September 1988; Series 2 (Box 59, Folder 4)
  - ABF-Change of Opertations, January, 1991; Series 2 (Box 59, Folder 5)
  - ALKO Express-"The Exhaust", November-December, 1940; Series 2 (Box 59, Folder 6)
  - American Steel, January 1981; Series 2 (Box 59, Folder 7)
  - American-Smith Freight, 1988-1990; Series 2 (Box 59, Folder 8)
  - America's Road Team, 1990; Series 2 (Box 59, Folder 9)
  - Anheuser-Busch Correspondence, 1992; Series 2 (Box 59, Folder 10)
  - Arthur B. Russell Jr.-unemployment Compensation Board of Review, January 9, 1992; Series 2 (Box 59, Folder 11)
  - Aycock Inc.-photo, 1986; Series 2 (Box 59, Folder 12)
  - Berkheimer Grievance & Civil Action Case, 1980-1981; Series 2 (Box 59, Folder 13)
  - Boy Scouts, 1989; Series 2 (Box 59, Folder 14)
  - Capital Bakers, 1985; Series 2 (Box 59, Folder 15)
  - Carolina Freight Carriers, 1989-1997; Series 2 (Box 59, Folder 16)
  - Central Storage and Transportation Co.-Legal Brief and News Clippings, May 1952-March 1954; Series 2 (Box 59, Folder 17)
  - Central Storage and Transfer Co.-Correspondence, 1981-1993; Series 2 (Box 59, Folder 18)
  - Chambers-Truman E Horner Inc., August 1987-April 1993; Series 2 (Box 59, Folder 19)
  - Chambers Develpment Co., 1989; Series 2 (Box 59, Folder 20)
  - Carges-Carolina Freight Carriers, 1991-1992; Series 2 (Box 59, Folder 21)
  - CF Motor Freight, 1991; Series 2 (Box 59, Folder 22)
  - Coca-Cola (Mid-Atlantic), 1988-1991; Series 2 (Box 59, Folder 23)
  - Co0nstruction Organizatong/Strike, 1938; Series 2 (Box 59, Folder 24)
  - Clyde Armstrong Roadway Express Photos, Late 1950s; Series 2 (Box 59, Folder 25)
  - Cumberland Valley School District, August, 1986; Series 2 (Box 59, Folder 26)
  - Dauphin County Prison-Local 776 Organizing, 1988-1991; Series 2 (Box 59, Folder 27)
  - Deborah Hospital Foundation, 1990; Series 2 (Box 59, Folder 28)
  - Drivers, Inc., 1989-1990; Series 2 (Box 59, Folder 29)
  - Earl Latsha Lumber Co.-Photo and nes articles, 1964; Series 2 (Box 59, Folder 30)
  - Eastern Expres, Inc.-Correspondence and Bankruptcy, 1974-1977; Series 2 (Box 60, Folder 1)
  - East Pennsboro, 1986-1987; Series 2 (Box 60, Folder 2)
  - ECD/Hugo/WST&C Correspondence, 1983-1985; Series 2 (Box 60, Folder 3)
  - ECT Bakery Policy Comm, 1986; Series 2 (Box 60, Folder 4)
  - E.K. Cheese Co., 1986-1987; Series 2 (Box 60, Folder 5)
  - Family Physician Associates-Drug Demonstrations, 1985; Series 2 (Box 60, Folder 6)
  - FBI Embezzlement Probe-Local 776, October, 1983-January 1985; Series 2 (Box 60, Folder 7)
  - Frank's Nursery and Crafts, March, 1990; Series 2 (Box 60, Folder 8)
  - Friedman, Richard, 1984; Series 2 (Box 60, Folder 9)
  - General Tire, October, 1988; Series 2 (Box 60, Folder 10)
  - Giant, December, 1990; Series 2 (Box 60, Folder 11)
  - Goodwill Newsletter, Winter, 1970; Series 2 (Box 60, Folder 12)
  - Hall's Motor Transit Co.-articles and correspondence, 1969-1990; Series 2 (Box 60, Folder 13)
  - Harrisburg Area Community College, 1989-1990; Series 2 (Box 60, Folder 14)
  - Harrisburg Central Labor Council Blood Bank, 1990; Series 2 (Box 60, Folder 15)
  - 1938 Harrisburg Grocery Strike, Series 2 (Box 60, Folder 16)
  - Harrisburg Produce Strike, December 1946-November 1948; Series 2 (Box 60, Folder 17)
  - Helms-Pittsburg Press Highway Transportation Forum, 1939-1951; Series 2 (Box 60, Folder 19)
  - Hershey Chocalate Co. /Paul Carnathan Letter to Editor, November 1st, 1958; Series 2 (Box 60, Folder 20)
  - Hess, 1990; Series 2 (Box 60, Folder 21)
  - Highspire, March 25, 1988; Series 2 (Box 60, Folder 22)
  - Highway Film Delivery, Inc., 1984-1986; Series 2 (Box 60, Folder 23)
  - Hilty Tank, 1984; Series 2 (Box 60, Folder 24)
  - Iceland Seafood Corp., November, 1988; Series 2 (Box 60, Folder 25)
  - IML Freight. Inc. Correspondence, 1984; Series 2 (Box 60, Folder 26)
  - Inter-Union Correspondence, August-October 1950; Series 2 (Box 60, Folder 27)
  - Keebler, undated; Series 2 (Box 60, Folder 28)
  - Local 463-Kaiser Correspondence, September 23, 1949; Series 2 (Box 60, Folder 29)
  - Local 776 Correspondence and News Clippings, 1950-1954; Series 2 (Box 60, Folder 30)
  - Labor Organizing-Pennsylvania Labor Relations Board, 1946-1947; Series 2 (Box 60, Folder 31)
  - Lawyers, 1989-1993; Series 2 (Box 60, Folder 32)
  - L.B. Smith Inc. Correspondence, February 1947-January 1948; Series 2 (Box 60, Folder 33)
  - Leo Oshinki Correspondence and Grievance Reports, May 1947-June 1949; Series 2 (Box 60, Folder 34)
  - Liberty Transportation, December, 1988; Series 2 (Box 60, Folder 35)
  - Liquid Carbonic Speciality Gas Corp, November, 1987; Series 2 (Box 60, Folder 36)
  - Make-A-Wish Foundation, 1991-1992; Series 2 (Box 60, Folder 37)
  - Middle Atlantic Millwork Co., 1991-1992; Series 2 (Box 60, Folder 39)
  - Middletown Borough, November, 1984; Series 2 (Box 60, Folder 40)
  - Motor Freight Express Photos, 1950s; Series 2 (Box 60, Folder 41)
  - Motor Freight Express, Inc., 1993; Series 2 (Box 60, Folder 42)
  - MotorCycle Insurance, 1991; Series 2 (Box 61, Folder 1)
  - M&G Convoy Inc. Correspondence, June-December 1948; Series 2 (Box 61, Folder 2)
  - MFX Road Logs, August, 1979; Series 2 (Box 61, Folder 3)
  - New Penn, September, 1992; Series 2 (Box 61, Folder 4)
  - NMFA-Union Business, 1987-1989; Series 2 (Box 61, Folder 5)
  - Pepsi Cola Co.-Files and Correspondence, December 1949-March 1951; Series 2 (Box 61, Folder 6)
  - Pennsylvania Commercial Drivers Conference, May 1947-April 1948; Series 2 (Box 61, Folder 8)
  - Pennsylvania State University, 1987; Series 2 (Box 61, Folder 9)
  - Pennsylvania Supply Co. Labor Dispute, July-August 1946; Series 2 (Box 61, Folder 10)
  - Pennsylvania Truck Lines [1], August 1987-March 1990; Series 2 (Box 61, Folder 11)
  - Pennsylvania Truck Lines [2], 1991-1992; Series 2 (Box 61, Folder 12)
  - Pennsy Supply, Inc., October, 1990; Series 2 (Box 61, Folder 13)
  - Perk Food Closing, 1988-1990; Series 2 (Box 61, Folder 14)
  - Perry County Courthouse, 1985-1989; Series 2 (Box 61, Folder 15)
  - Perry County Prison, 1992-1993; Series 2 (Box 61, Folder 16)
  - Pilot Freight Carriers, Inc., 1987-1989; Series 2 (Box 61, Folder 17)
  - Pittsburgh Plate Glass, 1989-1990; Series 2 (Box 61, Folder 18)
  - Rauch Transportation Co. Grievance Report, May 1942-March 1947; Series 2 (Box 61, Folder 19)
  - Rite Aid-Newsclippings and Correspondence, 1970-1993; Series 2 (Box 61, Folder 20)
  - Roadway Express, Inc., 1969-1993; Series 2 (Box 61, Folder 21)
  - Ryder Truck Rental and Leasing, 1988; Series 2 (Box 61, Folder 22)
  - Quaker Dress Company-Correspondence, May-July 1949; Series 2 (Box 61, Folder 23)
  - Quigley Millwork Correspondence, August, 1950; Series 2 (Box 61, Folder 24)
  - Richards Motor Freight Lines Correspondence, December 1946-August 1947; Series 2 (Box 61, Folder 25)
  - Rohr Bus Service, undated; Series 2 (Box 61, Folder 26)
  - Shirks Motor Express Corp.-"Singing Tire" Article, February, 1951; Series 2 (Box 62, Folder 1)
  - St. Johnsbury Trucking Co., 1993; Series 2 (Box 62, Folder 2)
  - Stoner Beverage Co.-Arbritage and Take-over, August, 1970; Series 2 (Box 62, Folder 3)
  - Stricland Transportation Co. Correspondence, November 1967-July 1969; Series 2 (Box 62, Folder 4)
  - Stroehman Brothers' Baking co., 1970-1993; Series 2 (Box 62, Folder 5)
  - Super Rite Foods, 1987-1993; Series 2 (Box 62, Folder 6)
  - Susquehanna Township, 1992; Series 2 (Box 62, Folder 7)
  - Thomas Industries Inc.-newsclippings, October 7, 1987; Series 2 (Box 62, Folder 8)
  - Tidewater Inland Express-Correspondence, 1972-1978; Series 2 (Box 62, Folder 9)
  - Tose-Fowler Inc. Strike and Closing, 1989; Series 2 (Box 62, Folder 10)
  - Tower Holmes Inc., 1985-1990; Series 2 (Box 62, Folder 11)
  - TransAmerica Freight Lines Inc., 1937-1968; Series 2 (Box 62, Folder 12)
  - Transcon Line Dispatch, 1988-1989; Series 2 (Box 62, Folder 14)
  - Transcontinental-Bankruptcy, 1990; Series 2 (Box 62, Folder 15)
  - Turnpike Extension, September 13, 1948; Series 2 (Box 62, Folder 16)
  - United Ice and Coal. co. Employee Case, October-November 1946; Series 2 (Box 62, Folder 17)
  - United Fund-Teamsters Photos, Late 1950s; Series 2 (Box 62, Folder 18)
  - United Restaurant Equipment, March 23, 1987; Series 2 (Box 62, Folder 19)
  - United Mineworkers Association, 1993; Series 2 (Box 62, Folder 20)
  - UPS-newsclippings and correspondence, 1976-1993; Series 2 (Box 62, Folder 21)
  - Wards Trucking, May 1985; Series 2 (Box 62, Folder 22)
  - Weather Shield MFG-Camp Hill Division, 1987; Series 2 (Box 62, Folder 23)
  - West Hanover Township, January, 1983; Series 2 (Box 62, Folder 24)
  - W.I. Womeldorf & Sons Co. Correspondence, November, 1955; Series 2 (Box 62, Folder 25)
  - Wilson Freight Co., 1978-1980; Series 2 (Box 62, Folder 26)
  - Wilson & Co. newsclipping, May 14, 1965; Series 2 (Box 62, Folder 27)
  - Work Rules-Harrisburg Motor Carriers Association, undated; Series 2 (Box 62, Folder 28)
  - W& L Beer Distributors-Union Busting Seminar, 1985; Series 2 (Box 62, Folder 29)
  - Wright-Abott Corp. Correspondence, June-August 1948; Series 2 (Box 62, Folder 30)
  - Yankee Lines Linc. Correspondence, February-May 1951; Series 2 (Box 62, Folder 31)
  - Yellow Cab, 1992; Series 2 (Box 62, Folder 32)
  - Local 46, Undated; Series 2 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Hunts Point Market, 1994; Series 2 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Teamsters History - 282 News, Undated; Series 2 (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Local History - 282, Undated; Series 2 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Local 299, Undated; Series 2 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - IBT History, 1977; Series 2 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - ECT Convention, 1978; Series 2 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - What's The Teamsters Union, 1978; Series 2 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - 75 Years, 1978; Series 2 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - News, 1979; Series 2 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Teamster News, 1980; Series 2 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Trucking, 1980; Series 2 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Forbes/Central States, 1980; Series 2 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Election, 1980; Series 2 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - After Fitz, 1980; Series 2 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - News, 1981; Series 2 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - ECT Power Struggle, 1982; Series 2 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Teamsters, 1983; Series 2 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - News, 1982; Series 2 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Tanker Strike, 1983; Series 2 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - News, 1983; Series 2 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - IBT History, 1983; Series 2 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - IBT History, 1984; Series 2 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - International Teamster Merger, 1984-1985; Series 2 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - IBT Visits ITU, 1984; Series 2 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Teamster Historical Notes, 1985; Series 2 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - News, 1985; Series 2 (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - ECT Convention, 1986; Series 2 (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Merger AFL-CIO, 1987; Series 2 (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - Presser Pictures, 1987; Series 2 (Box 5, Folder 27)